POKAI HUANG

Design Verification Engineer

0932732142

pokaihuang.tw@gmail.com

https://pkhuang-tw.github.io/

https://github.com/PKhuang-TW

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced engineer with 1 year in design verification and 3.5 years in firmware development. Skilled in collaborating with clients to define test plans and design test vectors, and experienced in working closely with inhouse designers for efficient debugging. Familiar with FPV and using SVA to verify submodule behaviors. Highly self-motivated, dedicating personal time to mastering UVM library internals and building UVM VIPs to strengthen practical and theoretical understanding.

EXPERIENCE

Design Verification Engineer | Phison Electronic

06/2024 - Present

- UFS underlying IP (Unipro) design verification
- Develop UVM environment for DUT
- Formal Property Verification (FPV)
- Design test plans and testvectors
- Discuss and modify test plans with international clients
- Verifying in-house DUTs and collaborating with designers on debugging

Firmware Engineer | Silicon Motion

01/2021 - 05/2024

- Develop Security features according to TCG specification
- Design Security features Test Plan & verify
- Customize requirements & Firmware debug
- Modularize features into Libraries for easier project management
- Develop automation scripts to improve working efficiency

EDUCATION

National Chiao Tung University - Hsinchu

09/2018 - 11/2020

Master - Institute of Computer Science And Engineering

National Central University - Taoyuan **Bachelor** – Department of Communication Engineering 09/2013 – 06/2017